Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence and memorabilia of Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1972-1979; Accession 1980-A-013
  - Correspondence
    - Campus police (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Cannon (Beelman) Retirement (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Carnegie Corporation - Carnegie Council on Children (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Carroll, Richard C.- (Associate Secretary) (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Central mailing service (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Chaplain's Office (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Chemistry Department (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Chicago students (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Christmas closing, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Chubb Fellowship (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - City and Its Environment, The (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Civil defense (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Classified information (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Coeducation report - Cresap, McComick and Paget (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Coeducation survey - Dartmouth (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Colleges, children's playground (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - College masters, housing (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Colleges, residential (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Colleges, residential fellowships (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Commencement, Reunions and Seminar, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 122 - 123)
    - Commencement, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Comptroller's Office (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Computer center (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Connecticut Agricultural - Experiment Station (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Connecticut Education Commissioner (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Connecticut Mental Health Center (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - Corporation - Alumni Fellow (Box 6, Folder 131)
      Restricted until January 1, 2026
      - 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 132 - 133)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 134 - 135)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 136)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 6)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 137)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 138 - 139)
      - Election (Box 7, Folder 140)
      - Election Voters (Box 7, Folder 141)
      - Women graduation for the Alumni Fellow Ballot, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 142)
      - Council of Masters, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 144 - 146)
      - Council, Yale College (student) (Box 7, Folder 147)
      - Creative Arts Workshop (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - Current needs of Yale (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - D - general (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - Dartmouth College (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon and Zeta Psi buildings (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - DeVane Professorship (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - Development Campaign Yale revisited (Box 7, Folder 155)
    - Development, Capital Campaign (Box 7, Folder 156)
    - Development, Capital Campaign (Box 8, Folder 157)
    - Development and Capital Support, general (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - Development Office (Box 8, Folder 159)
    - Dining halls, Firehouse Pub (Box 8, Folder 160)
    - Diplomas (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Directories (Box 8, Folder 162)
    - Divinity School (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - Divinity School intern (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - Drama School (Box 8, Folder 168)
    - Drug Dependence Institute (Box 8, Folder 169)
    - Dwight Chapel (Box 8, Folder 170)
    - E - general (Box 8, Folder 171)
    - Eli International (Box 8, Folder 172)
    - Embezzlement procedure (Box 8, Folder 173)
    - Emeritus Policy draft, 1972 October 18 (Box 8, Folder 174)
    - England, places for rent (Box 8, Folder 175)
    - Enlightenment, Congress on the, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 176 - 178)
    - F -general (Box 8, Folder 179 - 180)
    - Faculty Club (Box 9, Folder 181)
    - Faculty Handbook (Box 9, Folder 182)
    - Fanton, Jonathan (Box 9, Folder 183)
    - Fellowships (Box 9, Folder 184)
    - Financial Aid Office (Box 9, Folder 185)
    - First Church of Christ, New Haven (Box 9, Folder 187)
    - Ford visit (Box 9, Folder 189)
    - Foreign Students and Scholars - Advisor Office (Box 9, Folder 190)
    - Forestry School (Box 9, Folder 191)
    - France, Ambassador of (Box 9, Folder 192)
    - Franklin, Benjamin Papers (Box 9, Folder 194)
    - Freedom of Expression Committee, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 195 - 196)
    - Freedom of Expression Committee (Box 9, Folder 197)
    - Freshman year (Box 9, Folder 198)
    - Funerals and acknowledgments (Box 9, Folder 199)
    - G - general (Box 9, Folder 200)
    - Gay Alliance (Box 9, Folder 202)
    - George and Harry's (Box 9, Folder 203)
    - German Consulate, Boston (Box 9, Folder 204)
    - German Department (Box 9, Folder 205)
    - Germany and Yale (Box 9, Folder 206)
    - Gibbs Society (Box 10, Folder 208)
    - Gift and grant lists (Box 10, Folder 209)
    - Gifts in kind (Box 10, Folder 210)
    - Glee Club (Box 10, Folder 211)
    - Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, Association of (Box 10, Folder 212)
    - Graduate Club Association (Box 10, Folder 213)
    - Graduate-Professional Student Senate (Box 10, Folder 214)
    - "Graduate and Professional, The Yale" (Box 10, Folder 215)
    - Graduate School (Box 10, Folder 216)
    - Grounds maintenance (Box 10, Folder 218)
    - Guides (Box 10, Folder 219)
    - Gymnasium, Payne Whitney (Box 10, Folder 220)
    - H - general (Box 10, Folder 221)
    - Halloween (Box 10, Folder 222)
    - Harvard/Princeton/Yale Secretaries (Box 10, Folder 223)
    - Harvard University (Box 10, Folder 224)
    - Havemeyer House (Box 10, Folder 225)
    - Health Services Center (Box 11, Folder 226)
    - Hill Day Care Center, Calvin (Box 11, Folder 227)
    - Hillhouse Avenue Association (Box 11, Folder 229)
    - Hillhouse Avenue # 35 (Box 11, Folder 230)
    - Historic Commission (Box 11, Folder 231)
    - Historic Preservation, National Trust (Box 11, Folder 232)
    - Historical Series Committee (Box 11, Folder 233)
    - History of Art (Box 11, Folder 234)
    - Hockey Association, Yale (Box 11, Folder 235)
    - Hoosac School (Box 11, Folder 237)
    - Hospice (Box 11, Folder 238)
    - Housing - Overcrowding (Box 11, Folder 239)
    - I - general (Box 11, Folder 240)
    - Identification Cards (Box 11, Folder 241)
    - Information Office (Box 11, Folder 242)
    - Institution for Social and Policy Studies (Box 11, Folder 243)
    - International Association of Universities (Box 11, Folder 244)
    - International Office (Box 11, Folder 245)
    - International Student Center (Box 11, Folder 246)
    - Investments, University Proxy Questions (Box 11, Folder 247)
    - Ivy Group Secretaries (Box 11, Folder 248)
    - J - general (Box 11, Folder 249)
    - Japanese Sumitorno Gift (Box 11, Folder 250)
    - K - general (Box 11, Folder 251)
    - Keating Testimonial Dinner (Box 11, Folder 252)
    - Kent School (Box 11, Folder 253)
    - Keys (Box 11, Folder 254)
    - L - general (Box 12, Folder 257)
    - Law Jobs (Box 12, Folder 258)
    - Law Journal (Box 12, Folder 259)
    - Law School (Box 12, Folder 260)
    - Letters to legislators, etc. from Yale community (Box 12, Folder 262)
    - Library (Sterling Memorial) (Box 12, Folder 263)
    - Lists, Departmental Chairman for official functions (Box 12, Folder 265)
    - Lux et Veritas, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 266)
    - M - general (Box 12, Folder 267)
    - Mac - Mc - general (Box 12, Folder 268)
    - Mailing lists and campus mail rules (Box 12, Folder 269)
    - Map, Yale (Box 12, Folder 270)
    - Marsh Botanical Garden (Box 12, Folder 271)
    - Maternity Leave Policy (Box 13, Folder 272)
    - Mecha Budget Committee, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 273)
    - Medal, Yale (Box 13, Folder 274)
    - Medal Committee, Yale
      - 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 275)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 276)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 277)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 278)
    - Media Design Studio (Box 13, Folder 279)
    - Media Policy (Box 13, Folder 280)
    - Medical School (Box 13, Folder 281)
    - Modern Language Association, New England Convention (Box 13, Folder 283)
    - Morse College (Box 13, Folder 284)
    - Mory's (Box 13, Folder 285)
    - Motels, dormitories (Box 13, Folder 286)
    - Motor Vehicle Policy (Box 13, Folder 287)
    - Music School (Box 13, Folder 288)
    - N - general (Box 13, Folder 289)
    - National Academy of Sciences (Box 13, Folder 290)
    - National Humanities Institute (Box 13, Folder 291)
    - New Blues (Box 13, Folder 292)
    - New Haven Bicentennial Committee, Yale's (Box 13, Folder 293)
    - New Haven Foundation (Box 13, Folder 294)
    - New Haven Preservation Trust (Box 13, Folder 295)
    - New Haven Yale Club, Tennis (Box 13, Folder 296)
    - New York Giants
      - 1973 (Box 13, Folder 297)
      - 1973 (cont'd) (Box 14, Folder 298 - 299)
      - 1975 (Box 14, Folder 300)
    - New York Jets (Box 14, Folder 301)
    - Nursing School (Box 14, Folder 302)
    - O - general (Box 14, Folder 303)
    - Officers Retirement Plan (Box 14, Folder 304)
    - Old Campus (Box 14, Folder 305)
    - Oldest living graduates (Box 14, Folder 306)
    - P - general (Box 14, Folder 307)
    - Parent's day (Box 14, Folder 308)
    - Parking Authority (Box 14, Folder 309)
    - Peabody Museum (Box 14, Folder 310)
    - Pension Committee (Box 14, Folder 311)
    - Personnel Office (Box 15, Folder 312)
    - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 15, Folder 313)
    - Pierson, George (Box 15, Folder 314)
    - Yale: a Short History (Box 15, Folder 315)
    - Pierson, George - "Yale: a Short History" (Box 15, Folder 316 - 317)
    - Pierson, George - Yale History Office (Box 15, Folder 318 - 319)
    - Poland, Yale Committee on Cultural Relations (Box 15, Folder 320)
    - Policies (University) (Box 15, Folder 321)
    - Political Union (Box 15, Folder 322)
    - Political Union - Palestine Liberation Organization (Box 15, Folder 323)
    - Portraits (University) (Box 15, Folder 324)
    - Portraits (University) (Box 15, Folder 325)
    - Postage meter, advertising (Box 15, Folder 326)
    - Poster locations (Box 15, Folder 327)
    - Press, Yale University (Box 16, Folder 328)
    - Press, Board of Governors
      - 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 329)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 330)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 331)
    - President's Office (Box 16, Folder 332)
    - Princeton University (Box 16, Folder 333)
    - Printing Service, University (Box 16, Folder 334 - 335)
      - Greer Allen (Box 16, Folder 336)
    - Printing Service, University - Harkness Memorial Tower Woodcut (Box 16, Folder 337)
    - Printing Service Users Committee (Box 16, Folder 338)
    - Prom (Box 16, Folder 339)
    - Provosts Office (Box 16, Folder 340)
    - Psychiatric Institute (Box 16, Folder 341)
    - Publications, Yale (Box 16, Folder 342)
    - Public Information, Office of - Flink (Box 16, Folder 343)
    - Puerto Rican's Despierta Boricua (Box 16, Folder 344)
    - Puerto Rico, Governor of (Box 16, Folder 345)
    - Purchasing (Box 16, Folder 346)
    - Q - general (Box 16, Folder 347)
    - R - general (Box 16, Folder 348)
    - Receptions (Box 16, Folder 350)
    - Recommendation letters - College Deans and Graduate Schools (Box 16, Folder 351)
    - Records, Faculty and Students (Box 16, Folder 352)
    - Record keeping (Box 16, Folder 353)
    - Record, Official University (Box 16, Folder 354)
    - Religious Ministry at Yale (Box 16, Folder 356)
    - Religious Studies (Box 16, Folder 357)
    - Reports (annual) (Box 16, Folder 358)
    - Rotary Club (Box 17, Folder 359)
    - Rotary Club (Box 17, Folder 360)
    - Rotary Club, Program Committee (Box 17, Folder 361)
    - Rotary, program speakers (Box 17, Folder 362)
    - Roxbury Latin School (Box 17, Folder 363)
    - Russian Chorus (Box 17, Folder 364)
    - U -general (Box 17, Folder 365 - 366)
    - Sailing Associates, Yale (Box 17, Folder 367)
    - Saybrook College (Box 17, Folder 368)
    - Scholarships (Box 17, Folder 369)
    - Scholarship plan for sons and daughters of Yale Faculty and staff (Box 17, Folder 370)
    - Science and Engineering Association, Yale (Box 17, Folder 371)
    - Secondary Schools, private (Box 17, Folder 372)
    - Secretary's office (Box 17, Folder 373)
    - Secretary's office staff (Box 17, Folder 374)
    - Seven Springs advisory Committee (Box 17, Folder 375)
    - Seven Springs Farm Center
      - 1974 (Box 17, Folder 376)
      - 1975 (Box 17, Folder 377)
      - 1975 (Box 18, Folder 378)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 379)
    - Seven Springs Farm, Green J. N. (Box 18, Folder 380)
    - Sex at Yale (Box 18, Folder 381)
    - "She" (Box 18, Folder 382)
    - Sheffield Scientific School (Box 18, Folder 383)
    - Shockley Debate (Box 18, Folder 384 - 385)
    - Shuttle bus information (Box 18, Folder 386)
    - Sigma Xi (Box 18, Folder 387)
    - Silliman College (Box 18, Folder 388)
    - Skillman Associates (Box 18, Folder 389)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 18, Folder 391)
    - Sprague Hall (Box 18, Folder 392)
    - Stack Family (Box 18, Folder 393)
    - Stamps, special issue (Box 18, Folder 394)
    - Stiles College, Ezra (Box 18, Folder 395)
    - Strike, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 397)
    - Student affairs (Box 18, Folder 398)
    - Student agencies, associated (Box 18, Folder 399)
    - Student Loans (Box 18, Folder 400)
    - Summer jobs (Box 18, Folder 401)
    - Summer programs, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 402)
    - Summer term, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 403)
    - Summer term, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 404)
    - T - general (Box 19, Folder 405)
    - Travel office, University (Box 19, Folder 407)
    - Treasurer's office (Box 19, Folder 408 - 409)
    - U - general (Box 19, Folder 411)
    - Union, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 412)
    - United States, Seal of the (Box 19, Folder 413)
    - United Way, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 414)
    - University Council, general (Box 19, Folder 415)
    - University News Bureau (Box 19, Folder 416)
    - University Operations office (Box 19, Folder 417)
    - University-Wide Tribunal (Box 19, Folder 418)
    - Upward Bound (Box 19, Folder 419)
    - V - general (Box 19, Folder 420)
    - W - general (Box 19, Folder 421)
    - W - general (Box 19, Folder 422)
    - Walpole's correspondence - Yale edition (Box 19, Folder 423)
    - Walpole Jubilee folder # 1 - (PGC has #2) (Box 19, Folder 424)
    - Weekly Bulletin and Calendar (Box 19, Folder 425)
    - Wiggin and Dana (Box 19, Folder 426)
    - Women, Admission to Yale College report (Box 19, Folder 427)
    - Women, Administrative Internships (Box 19, Folder 428)
    - Women, Administrators at Yale (Box 19, Folder 429)
    - Women, Education of (Box 19, Folder 430)
    - Women Faculty members (Box 20, Folder 431)
    - Women, general (Box 20, Folder 432)
    - Women, Information and Counseling Service (Box 20, Folder 433)
    - Woodbridge Hall (Box 20, Folder 434)
    - Woolsey Hall (Box 20, Folder 436)
    - Woolsey Hall fees (Box 20, Folder 437)
    - XYZ - general (Box 20, Folder 439)
    - Yale Blue (Box 20, Folder 440)
    - Yale Center for British Art and British Studies (Box 20, Folder 441)
    - Yale-China Association (Box 20, Folder 442)
    - Yale Coat of Arms (Box 20, Folder 443)
    - Yale College (Box 20, Folder 444)
    - Yale College Dean's Office (Box 20, Folder 445)
    - Yale Co-op Corporation (Box 20, Folder 446)
    - Yale Daily News (Box 20, Folder 447)
    - Yale Daily News, Police Board (Box 20, Folder 448)
    - Yale-in-China film, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 449)
    - Yale memorials booklet (Box 20, Folder 450)
    - Yale Name, Protection of (Box 20, Folder 451)
    - Yale Psychiatric Institute (YPI) (Box 20, Folder 452)
    - Yale Reports (Box 20, Folder 453)
    - Yale Scene Series (Box 20, Folder 454)
    - Yale Seal (Box 20, Folder 455)
    - Yale Station (Box 20, Folder 456)
    - Yale Symphony (Box 20, Folder 457)
    - Yale University Women's Organization (Box 20, Folder 458)
    - YMCA (Young Men's Christian Association) (Box 20, Folder 459)
    - Yugoslavian Consul General (Box 20, Folder 460)
    - Miscellaneous, booklets, photographs (Box 20, Folder 461)
  - Telephone log books
    Existence and Location of Originals
    Deaccessioned 2/27/2015
  - Univesrsity Memorabilia
    - "A Salute to Bart Giamatti Dinner Program, attendees, list copy of musical tribute", 1979 January 6 (Box 25, Folder 504)
    - Committee on Organization and Management of Administrative Services (Final report), 1978 March 27 (Box 25, Folder 505)
    - National Register of Historical Places, Certificates for Connecticut Hall, Marsh House, Dana House, 1979 May (Box 25, Folder 506)
    - Noss, Luther, The History of the Yale School of Music, 1979 March (Box 25, Folder 507)
    - Photographs (15), president 's house, 43 Hillhouse Avenue, 1979 July 5 (Box 25, Folder 508)
    - Stiles, Ezra, letter, 1878 March 1 (Box 25, Folder 509)
    - Tropical scene wall hanging (bamboo sticks) from Right Reverend Sunder Clarke, Bishop in Madras for the church of South India, 1979 May 30 (Box 25, Folder 510)
    - Letter and Richard C. Lee's "A Grim Fairy Tale" dedicated to Vincent Sirabella for farewell dinner, 1979 June 26 (Box 26, Folder 511)
    - Yale medal photographs 16" X 20, 1976 (Box 27)
- Honorary degree records maintained by Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1969-1974; Accession 1981-A-028
  - 1969
    - Correspondence
      - A-F, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - G, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - H, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - I-M, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - N-R, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - S, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - T-Z, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Citations: samples, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8 - 9)
    - Drafts and Final Citations, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Holden, Reuben A., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 11 - 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1970
    - Correspondence
      - A-B, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - C-E, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - F, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - G- J, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - K-I, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - N-R, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - S, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - S-Z, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Acceptances and reports, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Citations, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Commencement luncheon, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Holden, Reuben A., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 26 - 29)
  - 1971
    - Correspondence
      - A-C, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - D-E, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - F-K, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - L-R, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - S-Z, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 1972
    - Correspondence
      - A-C, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - D-G, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - H-L, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - M-N, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - O-P, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - O-R, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - S-Z, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Addresses of recipients, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Biographies of candidates, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Citations, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Committee, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Hosts, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Letters and memoranda, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Lists, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Memorandum to new members, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Photograph, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Honorary Degree Recipients
      - Bellow, Saul, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 54)
      - Ford, Henry, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 56)
      - Huxtable, Ada Louise, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Honorary Degrees Not Received
      - Chavez, Cesar: declined, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - 1973
    - Correspondence
      - A-B, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - C-D, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - E-G, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - H, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - I -M, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 73)
      - N-R, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - S, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - T-W, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - X-Z, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Addresses of recipients, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Biographies, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Citations, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Committees, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Hosts, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Letters and memoranda, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Meetings 1st and 2nd, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 84 - 85)
    - Meetings 3rd and 4th, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 86 - 87)
    - Memorandum to new members, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Photograph, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Honorary Degree Recipients
      - Adams, Ansel (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Honorary Degrees Not Received
      - Olivier, Laurence: declined, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - 1974
    - Correspondence
      - A-B, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 108)
      - C, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 109)
      - D-E, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 110)
      - F-M, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 111)
      - N-P, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 112)
      - Q-R, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 113)
      - S, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 114)
      - T-Z, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Accommodations, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Biographies, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Citations, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Committee, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Luncheon, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Photograph, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Honorary Degree Recipients
    - Honorary Degrees Not Received
      - Marshall, Thurgood: declined, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 136)
- Information lists and mail synopses maintained by Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1974-1976; Accession 1981-A-029
  - Synopses of mail called "For Your Information" lists
    - 1974 Jul 2-1975 Feb 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1975 Feb 14 - 1975 Jul 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1975 Jul 24-1976 Feb 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1976 Feb 12-1976 Aug 3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Administrative files maintained by Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1970-1981; Accession 1981-A-030
  - Art Gallery, Governing Board (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Athletic candidates with distinction, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Governing Board (Box 1, Folder 4 - 6)
  - Camp Mahew (Box 1, Folder 7 - 9)
  - Chamber of Commerce
    - Charter Revision Commission
    - Commission membership (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Compensation of officials and employees (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Concept papers (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Consultants (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Draft proposals re: Feb meeting (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Education committee goals for New Haven (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Financial (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Meeting Minutes
      - 1981 Jan 12 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - 1981 Feb 3 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - 1981 Feb 10 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - 1981 Mar 3 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - 1981 Mar 10 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - 1981 Mar 13 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - 1981 Mar 24 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - 1981 Feb 17 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - News Media (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Procedures (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Public testimony (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Staff (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Subject areas: memoranda (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Timetable (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - West Hartford, Connecticut (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Communications Director search (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Connecticut Savings Bank: minutes of meetings (Box 3, Folder 34 - 35)
  - Connecticut Savings Bank: financial papers (Box 3, Folder 36 - 38)
  - DNA Research Program (Box 3, Folder 39 - 40)
  - Educational Investment Plan (Box 4, Folder 41 - 42)
  - Financial Aid officers, manual for (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Foreign Nationals at Yale University (Box 4, Folder 44 - 45)
  - Hiring Plan, Yale (clippings) (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Italy, the Story of: series of programs on television (Box 4, Folder 48 - 50)
  - Multiple Sclerosis Society (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - New Haven: general information (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - New Haven Bicentennial Commission (Box 5, Folder 54 - 57)
  - New Haven Bicentennial Committee (Box 5, Folder 58 - 59)